《越狱》前情回顾
Previously on Prison Break
请告诉我日落旅馆的号码?
Give me the number for a Sundown tel, please?
在新墨西哥州的吉拉有一个
Got one in Gila, New Mexico.
六月...三号  明天
6-3, Tomorrow.
是谁?
Who is this?
我想你应该知道的
I think you already know.
如果我在家里的后院埋了具尸体
But if I buried someone in my own backyard
我会老想着这事
I'd think about it all the time.
放过我和我的家人
Let me and my family disappear and in return
做为回报 我会替你保密
I'll keep your little secret.
我知道这完全出乎你的预料
I know it's not how you wanted this to play out.
有时候事情就是那么...难以控制
Sometimes things happen that are just...out of your control.
我们马上就会见面的 迈克尔
I'll see you soon, Michael.
比你想象的还要快
It just may be sooner than you think.
你不能在这儿出现!
You can't be here!
你妹妹呢? 我要见玛丽克鲁兹
Where's your sister?I need to see Maricruz.
婚礼会在2:30举行
The wedding's at 2:30.
玛丽克鲁兹 她对他说 不!
Maricruz, she told him, "no."
你能相信吗?
Can you believe that?
去吧 去找她
Go on, get your girl.
LJ!
都给我马上趴下! 趴下...
Both of you face down, now!Please...
疑犯逮到了
Suspect in custody.
可能是 林肯·布伦斯
Possible I.D.: Lincoln Burrows.
你得告诉我韦斯特莫兰德的钱在哪
You're going to tell me where you stashed Westmoreland's money
不然我就会像拔鸡毛那样
or I'm gonna pluck you like a chicken
把线一针一针的拆开
stitch-by-stitch
对一个百万富翁来说 你的行李也太少了点吧
for a millionaire, you travel light.
嘿
嘿 这是什么?
What is this?
是我用来量血压的
it's for my blood pressure.
看看我发现了什么
Look what I found.
我猜赫兰德太太很喜欢做肉饼啊
Guess Ms.Hollander liked to beat some meat.
或许  让我在你太阳穴上敲几下
Maybe a couple of whacks in the temple with this oney.
你就会想起钱放哪了
will help you remember where you put the m
嘿 我们已经打了这混蛋一晚上了
Hey, we've been beating his ass all night.
这不起什么作用
He ain't coming off the goods.
我们得想些其他的办法
We need to do something different.
不管你们对我做什么
It don't matter what you do to me.
我都不会说
I ain't talking.
那好 我们是不达目的绝不罢休
Well, I ain't stopping till I get what I came for.
来点音乐怎样?
How 'bout we listen to that again?
噢
Oh
现在你能告诉我钱在哪了吧?
now you're gonna tell me where that money is
要不你就把它带进坟墓里吧
or i'm gonna read it on your tombstone?
好吧...好吧 我给你点提示
okay...okay.We'll give you a little clue.
钱不在这儿
It ain't here.
确认了 布伦斯被逮到了
confirmed, Burrows is in custody.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
他千辛万苦到了亚利桑那州
He made it all the way to Arizona.
再过一天 他就可以跑掉了
Another day, he would have been gone.
找到马宏了吗?
You find Mahone?
没 打过去都是转到语音信箱的
No.Keep trying to call, it goes straight to voicemail.
我是亚历山大 马宏
This is Alexander Mahone.
有事请留言
Please leave a message.
金姆先生
Mr.Kim.
克里曼先生
Mr.Kellerman.
林肯·布伦斯被逮到了
Lincoln Burrows is in custody.
这就是我为什么打电话给你
That's the reason I called.
谁看着他?
Who has him?
威尔科克斯 亚利桑那州的警察
Wilcox, Arizona PD.
我们得马上把他弄出来
We need to extricate him, right away.
马宏先生在哪?
Where's Mr.Mahone?
我正在和他联系
I'm getting in touch with him right now
但我自己也可应付的
but I can take care of this one myself.
我们雇用马宏
This is why we hired Mr.Mahone.
就因为他是这里的官方人物
He's the official face here.
别担心 我不用通过官方途径
Don't worry. This won't be official,
也不会有任何问题
and there won't be any questions.
当然不会有问题
Of course, there will.
但一定要确保他们都给我闭嘴
Just make sure no one's left to answer them.
我儿子与此事无关 请放了他
My son had nothing to do with this, please.
法官会做出决定的
judge will decide that.
打过电话了吗?
是的 菲尼克斯那边正派人过来
You call ahead? Yeah, phoenix is sending backup.
我想这不是我们的人 吉米
I don't think it's one of ours, Jimmy.
怎么回事?!
What the hell?!
快!
come on!
跑 快跑!
Run, run!
过来!
Come here!
好吧 冷静点
Okay, calm down.
你要是敢再这样...
you y that again...
你们是谁?!
who the hell are you?!
我们是来帮你的!
We're on your side!
我们是你父亲的人
We're with your father.
马宏 林肯·布伦斯已被逮到了
Mahone, Lincoln Burrows has been apprehended.
-在哪里?  -亚利桑那
Where? Arizona.
我正过去 我要你也过去
I'm on my way and I need your talents, on the ground as well.
我会尽快到的
I'll get there as soon as I can.
我想你没听明白
I don't think you heard me.
马上去亚利桑那
Get to Arizona.
我就快逮到斯科菲尔德了
I'm this close to Scofield.
我们有他要找的人
We have a bird in the hand.
是的 我也有一个
Yeah, well, so might I.
你要我找出斯科菲尔德和唐克雷蒂的会面地点
You wanted me to figure out Scofield's rendezvous with Tancredi?
就在今天...
It's happening today...
...我现在就在他们要来的地方
and I'm sitting right on top of it.
你看什么?
what are you looking at?
这是哪?
Where are we?
别管是哪  这里很安全
It doesn't matter. You're safe here.
请坐
You can take a seat.
在没见到我爸前我不会配合
I ain't doing a thing until I see my dad.
据我所知  他已经在来这儿的路上了
All I can tell you is he's on his way.
他的飞机一小时后就到了
His flight lands in an hour.
我为什么要相信你  女士?
Why should I trust you, lady?
我看你没的选择
I don't see you have much of a choice.
如果你想的话 我可以把你交还给那些警察
I could drop you back off with the cops if you'd prefer.
你还有别处可去吗?
You have somewhere else to be?
事实上我们是有地方去
Matter of fact, we do.
你们不能走
We can't let you leave.
你父亲原以为你弟弟和你在一起他人呢?
And your father was expecting your brother to be with you. Do you know where he is?
你觉得我会告诉你吗?
Do you really think I'm going to answer that?
你得开始和我们合作  林肯
You need to start cooperating with us, Lincoln.
我们只是想帮你
We're only trying to help.
迈克尔 斯科菲尔德   一周前从福克斯河州立监狱逃了出来
Micheal Scofield, escaped from Fox River a week ago
没见过
No, never seen him.
那如果你见到了打这个电话
Well, if you do, please call me at that number.
好的
Will do.
沿着路下去还有家旅店
There's another hotel down the road.
谢了
Thanks.
什么事?
yeah?
你有份传真
You got a fax.
请从门下面塞进来好吗?
Uh, could you put it under the door, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
一小时后  巴特菲尔德路 16781号
1 hour 16781 Butterfield Road
特丽莎
Theresa.
是费尔南多 苏克雷
It's Fernando Sucre.
费尔南多
Fernando.
特丽莎
Theresa.
她不在这里
She's not here.
求你别挂
Plase don't hang up.
对不起...求你了
Please.
我需要知道些情况
I need to know something.
你现在有更麻烦的事得处理
You've got bigger problems than my sister right now.
不  不  等一下  拜托
No, no. Wait. Please. Please.
我必须要和她谈谈
I need to talk to her.
不可能的  我们下午就走了
lease. You can't. We're leaving this afternoon.
你们去哪儿?
Where you going?
墨西哥的伊克斯塔帕  一周后才会回来
Ixtapa, Mexico. We won't be back for a week.
也就是她和赫克特原计划度蜜月的地方
We're taking the honeymoon she had planned with Hector.
过一会儿她就来接我了
he's picking me up in a few hours.
-几点? -两点左右
What time? A little before 2:00
你一定要让她给我打个电话
she have to call me.Okay.
好吗?  我把号码给你
I'll give you the number.
你现在在哪儿?
Where are you?
别把我的名字写在电话号码前
Take this number off caller I.D.
拜托了 特丽莎
Please, Theresa,
让她给我打电话  好吗?
just have her call me, okay?
我会在这里等的
I'll be right here.
你好  莎拉
Hello, Sara.
我都不确定你会不会来
I wasn't sure you'd come.
我没得选择
I didn't have a choice.
我知道这对你来说不容易
This isn't going to be easy for you
你的留言说
You said in your message
你有计划可以解决好这一切
that you had a plan to make this right.
我想知道是什么计划
I need to know what that is.
没错  她昨晚入住的
Yeah, she checked in last night.
一个人?
Was she alone?
是的
Yeah.
凯莉 福斯特
Kelli Foster.
我给她开了9号房
I put her in room nine.
你是今早上想联系她的那个人?
You the guy that was trying to call this morning?
早上有人想联系她?
A guy tried to call this morning?
是啊  给她发了个传真
Yeah.He was trying to send her a fax.
是吗?
Did he do it?
是的  大概20分钟前
Yeah.20 minutes ago.
你的传真机有记录吗?
Does the fax have memory?
应该有
I guess so.
知道这是哪儿吗?
Do you know where that is?
离这里就5分钟的路
It's five minutes away.
如果她回来
Hey, if she comes back,
有什么要我做的吗?
is there anything you want me to do?
她不会回来了
She isn't coming back.
我已经安排好一起去巴拿马了
I've arranged for us to get to Panama.
明天我们就去和我哥哥会合
We're meeting up with my brother tomorrow
等下  这就是你的计划?
Wait.That's your plan?
逃到巴拿马去?
To run away to Panama
和两个美国头号通缉犯一起?
with the two most wanted men in America?
迈克尔  我来是因为
Michael, I came here because
我以为你会给我些象样的答案
I thought you were going to have real answers for me.
这就是答案
This is an answer.
这也是我们目前唯一的答案
And, right now, it's the only one we've got.
和一个欺骗过我的人一起亡命天涯?
Running away into the sunset with the man who lied to me?
是吗?
Really?
我是说你想过其他人吗?
I mean, did you know about the other guys?
你想过会把帝博格这种人
Did you know that I would be putting T-Bag
放回到大街上吗?
back out on to the street?
我从来也没想过会那样
I never meant for that to happen.
我在做一些不得不做的事
I was doing what I needed to do.
不然我哥哥就会死
My brother was going to die
可我父亲已经死了
Well, my father's dead
你父亲的事我很抱歉
I am sorry about your father.
对许多事情 我都感到很抱歉
I'm sorry for a lot of things.
对于你的那些事
For what I did to you.
我有很多很多的悔恨
I have many, many regrets
但那是最后悔的一个
but that's the biggest.
这已经于事无补了
it does not help me right now
这点我也很抱歉
I'm sorry for that, too.
我并不指望你...
I didn't expect you to, uh...
我并不指望你能原谅我
I didn't expect you forgive me.
但是我不想让你...
But I don't want you, to, uh...
不想让你独自来面对这一切
I don't want you to be alone in this.
我不想独自面对
I don't want to be alone.
我们走吧  快上车
let's go. get into the car
我们出不去了
You can't get out this way.
迈克尔 这是唯一一条出去的路
Go back is the only way out of here
我们就从这条路离开这里
That is where we are going.
坐稳了
Hold on.just hold on
-迈克尔你想干什么? -你坐稳就行了
Micheal, what r u doing? just hold on
你还好吗?
You all right?
他还在跟着我们
He's still behind us.
坐稳了
hold on
站起来  拜格威尔
On your feet, Bagwell.
看上去很热哦
Skewers are hot.
他有把钥匙!
he's got a key
我会拿到钥匙的  别逼我...
I'm going to get that key if I have to...
我们马上就会见到那钥匙了老兄
we're going to see that key again, friend.
马上就会见到它
We're going to see it real soon.
把信用卡还给我
Give me my credit card.
你都买了些什么?
What did you get me?
买了些什么?
What did you get?
李子汁 烟叶
Prune juice, smokes
一点儿沾酱
a little dip
还有一袋小水龟
and a bag of sliders
先来哪个?
What do you want first?
看起来象个爱嚼的家伙
Looks like a chew guy to me.
不许吐出来
No spitting.
他含过更糟的东西
He's had worse things in his mouth.
对于将来 你有何打算  费尔南多?
what do you want, Fernando, from the future?
你会跟我走吗?
Would you run if I said you?
如果我不愿意你会缠着我吗?
Would you chase me if I did?
我们得回车上去
we got to get back to my car.
太远了
It's too far.
如果我们不在他叫人来之前离开的话...
If we go now, before he gets more people...
他不会找人支援的
he's not gonna call for backup.
他要保守秘密
he wants his privacy.
怎么回事?
Why?
他不是来抓我的
He's not trying to catch me.
他是来杀我的
He's trying to kill me.
你爷爷
Your grandfather.
因为他我才被陷害的
He was the reason I was set up in the first place.
他以前为那些想我死的人工作
He used to work for the people wh wanted me dead.
这些事情都是因为他
This is all just to get to him.
你父亲应该马上就到了
Your father should be arriving any minute.
你叫简  对吗?
Jane, right?
对不起
Sorry.
没关系的
Don't worry about it.
你了解我爸吗?
You know my dad?
了解很多?
足够多
Well enough.
我们以前共事过
We used to work together.
在公司里
Ah, the company.
对
Yeah.
但那是很早前的事了
But that was a long time ago.
现在我跟公司对着干  他也一样
And now I work against them, just like he does.
那我猜你也抛弃你的家庭了
So I guess you walked out on your family, too.
没解释  没道别
No explanations, no good-byes.
我没有家庭
I don't have a family.
林肯  他真的想见你和你弟弟
迈克尔10岁以后你爸爸就再没见过他了
He hasn't seen Michael since he was ten years old.
他们来了
They're here.
在这等下
Wait here.
我们去哪里?
Where are we going?
迈克尔从来没见过你爷爷
Michael never met your grandfather.
嗨
Hey
爸爸
Dad.
我不想被困在这里
I don't want to get trapped in here.
另外那头肯定有个出口
There's got to be an exit on the other side.
你继续走
You go on. Michael.
迈克儿  我会跟上你的  去吧
i'll be right behind u.Go.
有坏消息了
the news is not good.
在我来之前  林肯·布伦斯被截走了
Burrows was intercepted before I got here.
是有点挫折  但我们没被甩开太远
It is a setback, but we're not that far behind.
保罗 保罗 冷静 保罗  冷静
Paul, Paul, calm down.
没事了  会有人处理的
It'll be all right. Someone will take care of it.
有人  谁?
Someone... who?
比尔  别告诉我你--
ill, tell me you're not bringing someone else in on this.
--又找人介入了
你不会以为你是单枪匹马吧?
You didn't think you were alone on this, did you?
你只是个士兵
You're a soldier.
我们是支军队
There's an army.
你从莎拉那得到了什么消息?
Tell me, what do you have on Sara Tancredi?
这两件事有联系吗?
What does that have to do with this?
去完成你最初的工作
Go back to your original assignment.
比尔  这里有我  我能搞定  然后
Bill, I'm here now. I can do this,
那女的
and then... the girl.
我们要知道她父亲跟她说了什么
We need to know what her father told her.
你查清楚了  打我电话
When you find out, give me a call.
我是  凯乐门特工
This is agent kellerman.
给我查查莎拉的租车信息
I need that rental car information on Sara Tancredi.
好了  看这里
Yeah, this is it right here.
75英尺长的双柴油游艇
75-foot twin diesel azimut,
全景驾驶舱
flybridge, panoramics
有了这么一艘船  你就是个人物了
you pull up in a boat like that, you're somebody.
-让我看看 -别碰
- Let me see. - Get off.
感觉如何啊?
how ya doin', Bagwell?
去拿屎
Get the stool.
什么?
- What stool?
去拿他的大便
- The stool.
这是开某个汽车站储物柜的
It's from one of them lockers in a bus station.
我会尽量不去想这玩意之前到过哪
I'll try not to think about where it's been.
不不不  别这样  求你挂掉吧
no, no, no, no-- don't do that, now. Come on.
你好  请派个警察来
Hey, there. Send the police.
一个疯子闯进我家里来了
Some scumbag broke into my house.
对  马贝里山1505号 对 505 马泊里山庄
Yeah, 1505 Marberry Hill.
他还在吗?
- Is he still there?
在  你们最好快点
- Yeah, you better come quick.
上路吧  罗伊
let's hit it, roy.
求你了  别这样
Come on, now, please don't do this.
别  别把我就这么扔下好吗?
Don't-- just don't leave me like this, okay?
我可以带你们去拿钱  我知道在什么地方
I can take you right to the money, I know right where it is.
我也知道  再见
So do I. Adios.
求你了  别这样
I'm begging you, don't do this. Please!
求你了  咱们商量商量
Geary, come on, we can make a deal, man. Come on, come on.
-求你了 -没的商量
No deals.
你已经输掉最后一块筹码了  老弟
You just crapped out your last bargaining chip, pal.
拜托!
Please!
我要是你可不会这么做  亚历克斯
I wouldn't do that if I were you, Alex.
闻到了吗?
You smell that?
丙烷
It's propane.
到处都是
It's filling the room.
你一扣扳机
And if you pull that trigger,
我们都会死
we both die.
我会开枪的!
I'll do it!
可能吧
Maybe.
在那之前  我问你个问题
But before you do, let me ask you a question, Alex.
你认为你还算是个好人
Do you think you're still one of the good guys
在为正义而战吗?
fighting the good fight?
因为我想我们都明白你已经越线了
Because I think we both know you've crossed over.
你在错误的立场上追逐着错误的对象
You're on the wrong, side chasing the wrong guys.
我哥是无辜的
My brother is innocent.
他根本没杀过人
He never killed anyone.
多谢你让我看清这一切
Oh, thanks for opening my eyes.
行了 亚历克斯  开枪
Okay, Alex, shoot.
我们都知道接下来的事
We both know what will happen.
丙烷早晚会把我熏死  我开不开枪
The propane will kill me anyway,
又有什么差别  我到觉得现在正是时候
what difference does it make? Might as well do it right now.
言之有理
That's a good point.
好了吧
there. There!
这样就会给你点时间
That'll give you some time
来思考下你正在做的事
to think about what you're doing.
但首先给你句忠告  收手吧
But first, a word of advice: Stop.
因为你追得再近
Because when you get close,
到最后都是我赢
I will win every time.
你真这么想?
You think?
在笼子里的不是我
- I'm not the one in the cage.
对  不是你
- No, you're not.
你我之间有个很大的区别  迈克尔
There's one big difference between you and I, Michael.
你也刚证明了这点
And you just proved it.
你不杀人
You can't kill.
而只有杀了我才能阻止我
And that's what it's gonna take to stop me.
因为我不会象你这样有所保留
'Cause I don't have the same reservations.
我也不能那样
I can't.
所以要么就是现在在吉拉
So whether it's today in Gila
或者是明日在阿儿布克亦或是2月后...
or tomorrow in Albuquerque or two months from now...
在巴拿马
in Panama.
我会抓到你的
I will get you.
我没的选择
I don't have a choice.
我争取了点时间
I bought us some time.
你还好吗?  在流血呢
You okay? You're bleeding.
没事  我们走吧
Yeah, let's go.
系上安全带
Your seatbelt.
这儿  804
Here.
让开
Move.
这恐怕是你见过的最美的东西了吧?
Ain't that the most beautiful thing you ever seen?
全是钞票
All that green.
这比大峡谷还壮观
It's prettier than the grand canyon.
罗伊  这是历史性的一刻
You know, Roy, this is a monumental moment
对我们两个来说
for both
把包给我  贝利克
Hand over the bag, Bellick.
把锤子放下  老太太
Put down the pounder, grandma.
我不是在开玩笑
Hey, hey. I am not kidding around.
你以为就凭你那软骨头...?
Well, you think your pansy ass...
下次你去屎堆里掏吧
Next time, you pick through the crap.
好了 急救箱
Okay, first-aid kit
可丢弃的电话和几支牙刷
disposable phones, couple of toothbrushes.
旅店怎么样了?
What about the motel?
他们是按小时记费的不需要证件
They charge by the hour, so they didn't ask for id.
你拿着钥匙吗?
- Do you have the keys?
是的
- Yeah.
抱歉我们不在家
Sorry, we're not home.
在听到提示音后请留言
Leave a message at the beep
我们会给你回电
and we'll get back to you.
这个留言是给玛丽克鲁滋的
Listen. This message is for Maricruz.
我就在那里等你的电话
I was right there waiting for your call,
但是有警察来了我不能接电话
but the cops showed up and I couldn't pick up the phone.
我想这大概就是
I know probably that's the exact reason
你不想和我在一起的原因
why you may not want to be with me.
听我说
Listen to me.
我的姑姑达丽斯就住在墨西哥城外
My aunt Ldalyz, she lives outside Mexico city,
在山里面的一个农场里
in the mountains, on a farm,
有能让小孩骑的南美驼
with... with a llama for the baby to ride.
在下周
So, next week,
等你回家的时候
when you fly back home,
当你到机场的时候
when you go to the airport,
我会到机场去接你
I'll be there.
我会在伊克斯塔帕等你
n the airport. In Ixtapa I'll wait for you.
我向你保证  玛丽
I promise you, Marita.
我爱你玛丽  爱你超过一切
I love you, Mari.I love you more than anything
我不能没有你
and I can't live without you.
我知道的
I just know
我会想办法的  宝贝
I can make it work, baby.
这是给你路上用的
This is, uh, in case you run into trouble down the road.
万一有什么麻烦用的上
我有办法
I have a way.
她在哪儿?
- Where is she?
-谁? -玛丽克鲁滋
- Who? Maricruz.
她不在家也没去上班
She wasn't home and she's not at work.
她也不在这儿
Well, she's not here.
我不知道她在哪儿
I don't know where she is.
你想找麻烦吗  卡琳达?
You want problems, Kalinda?
别骗我
Don't lie to me.
她去墨西哥了  是不是?
She went to Mexico, didn't she?
去度我们的蜜月
And on our honeymoon.
还是我掏的钱
Paid for with my money.
可能会有些疼
This isn't gonna feel good.
我抗疼痛能力很高
I have a high tolerance for pain.
这你知道的
You know that.
是的
You do.
你也不是什么糖尿病人  是吧?
And you're not a diabetic, are you?
好吧
All right.
迈克尔  告诉我
Michael, tell me something.
你是不是觉得某种程度上你也很享受这些?
You think there's a part of you that enjoys this?
伤口上的双氧水?
不是
Peroxide in an open wound? No.
我是说整个越狱以及逃亡
I mean escaping from prison nd being on the run
这些危险和恐惧
and the danger and the fear
紧迫感等等这所有的一切
and the rush, all that.
这个...
It, uh...
这对我来说就好象...
it feels to me like...
有吸毒一样的快感
chasing a high.
还有...
And...
我知道这是什么感觉...
and I know what that's like and...
我现在应该更明白了
I should know better by now.
我从来没从这方面想过
I never thought about it like that.
我知道我跟你说过这句话
I know you've heard this before
但是不会一直这样下去的
but it won't always be like this.
从你跟我说的来看事情变得越来越糟
From everything you've told me, it's just getting worse.
他们不可能永远追我们
They can't chase us forever.
今天追我们这人
The guy who caught up with us today
他在边境就会停下
he stops at the border
所以我们必须要越境
and that's why we have to get across
我安排了合适的人来帮我们
And I have the people in place to help us do that
明天我们就去见他们
We're meeting them tomorrow.
就再等一天  莎拉
One more day, Sara.
就一天
One more day.
我只要求那么多
That's all I'm asking.
你去清洗一下吧
You can go get cleaned up.
不要把这里弄湿了
Keep this dry.
莎拉
Sara.
我很高兴你来了
I'm glad you came.
那么...
So...
就是这位
- This is him.
小林肯
- Lincoln, Jr.
你照自己的名字给他起的？
- You named him after yourself.
我不会给他起名艾尔多的
- I wasn't gonna name him Aldo.
LJ这是你爷爷
LJ, this is your grandfather
艾尔多 布伦斯
Aldo Burrows
我等这一刻已经很久了
Waited for this for a long time
我安排了一个安全的地方给你们去住
I've arranged a safe place for both of you to go to.
谢谢你把我们救出来但是  我们要去见迈克尔
他在哪儿?
Where is he?
在边境那儿一个叫波士瓦布丝的地方
Down by the border, a place called Bolshoi Booze.
我可以一个人去接他
- I can go alone and get him.
不行
- No.
情况变了
Things are different.
有些证据
There's some evidence.
我们只需要点时间
We just need a little more time
就能把整件事情公之于众...
and we can blow this whole thing wide open
但是没有时间了
but there is no time
我相信迈克尔 他有一个计划能  把我们都带到巴拿马去
I trust Michael he has a plan to get us to Panama
你不明白
You don't understand.
你们不需要去巴拿马
You don't need to go to Panama
不需要再逃亡了
You don't need to run anymore.
告诉我好消息吧
Tell me good news.
巴伦斯们都在  共三个
I got Burrows-- the trifecta.
搞定他们
- Take care of them.
斯科菲尔德怎么办?  他们要去见他
- What about Scofield? They're gonna meet him.
没关系的
It doesn't matter.
快去干掉他们
Do it now.
莎拉?
Sara?
这一次我更明白了  对不起...
The fine I know better I am sorry...
你好啊  莎拉
Hi Sara